Change history of DLSUdtp

*******
Future plans:

(1) Embed animation in the PDF file

(2) Add important guidelines from report_format_template.tex and Project 2016 T1 - Narrative and Systematic Review.txt

(3) Add the following for Ph.D. dissertation topic 

	Authors should consider the following points:
	1)	Technical papers submitted for publication must advance the state of knowledge and must cite relevant prior work. 
	2)	The length of a submitted paper should be commensurate with the importance, or appropriate to the complexity, of the work. For example, an obvious extension of previously published work might not be appropriate for publication or might be adequately treated in just a few pages.
	3)	Authors must convince both peer reviewers and the editors of the scientific and technical merit of a paper; the standards of proof are higher when extraordinary or unexpected results are reported. 
	4)	Because replication is required for scientific progress, papers submitted for publication must provide sufficient information to allow readers to perform similar experiments or calculations and use the reported results. Although not everything need be disclosed, a paper must contain new, useable, and fully described information. For example, a specimen’s chemical composition need not be reported if the main purpose of a paper is to introduce a new measurement technique. Authors should expect to be challenged by reviewers if the results are not supported by adequate data and critical details.
	5)	Papers that describe ongoing work or announce the latest technical achievement, which are suitable for presentation at a professional conference, may not be appropriate for publication.

(4) Add the following.

Students: Remember This

	• When printing from a pdf, you must select the option “Page scaling: None.” Otherwise Adobe will be “helpful” and mess up all margins. Printing from a dvi or printing pdfs at office services is safe.
	• Check for “widows,” “orphans,” and words that spill into the margin. These should be the most common formatting errors that LaTeX does not fix automatically.
	• Format checkers will mark English mistakes if they happen to see them, but they are not proofreaders. So passing the format check does not mean your spelling and grammar are correct, and mistakes that were not caught in one format check may be caught in another.
	• Good advice for feedback from proofreaders in general: When the format for a certain type of entry, say a section heading, is marked as “to be corrected” (long
	section headings are supposed to be in inverted pyramid form), it is best to check the format of all these entries, as the format needs to be consistent overall.

Notes for Proofreading and Format Checking of the LaTeX-based document output:

	We appreciate the services provided by proofreaders and format checkers to assure uniformly high quality of documents. Because of the differences between mathematical documents and other documents,
	we request that the following be kept in mind.

	• The LaTeX format was typeset using a DLSU ECE Department Approved Template. Therefore most formatting should be a non-issue.
	• Issues that should not require correction, except as indicated below.
		– Global margins, order of sections, page numbering, title page, format of headings, table of contents, list of figures, list of tables. (All approved when the template was created.)
		– LaTeX is the professional standard for mathematical typesetting. Equations are mostly typeset with the LaTeX default options.
		– Some built in font sizes cannot be changed. Font sizes for headings, etc., were approved, even if they may look a little different than in WORD documents.
	• Issues that require attention. There are some situations in which LaTeX automatic formatting is less than optimal.
		– Margin infractions on individual lines. The global margins have been approved, but if the program does not know how to split a long term, it can spill into the margin. This is especially likely in typeset equations and can and should be fixed.
		– Widows and orphans. Linebreaking is automatic and sometimes leaves the first line of a paragraph on the preceding page or puts the last line on the next page.
		– English spelling, grammar, punctuation, etc.
		– Gross infractions on the placement and spacing of figures.

	Because of the way LaTeX imports and creates images, the distance between a figure and its caption can vary slightly. Large white spaces should be
	flagged, though.


(5) Bulletize all instructions

*******
v2025.01.21 changes:

(1) Added standards in Chapter 4.
(2) Corrected some typos.

By: LM
*******

*******
v2022.02.19 changes:

(1) Changed ADRAS to Department Chair.
(2) Reflected DECE's new name.
(3) Changed JGCE to GCOE.

By: LM
*******

*******
v2020.10.22 changes:

(1) Changed GCOE to JGCE.
(2) Removed unnecessary Markups in the Word template.
(3) Corrected miswording in Table 6.1.
(4) Described erase_aux_files.cmd in _README.txt

By: LM
*******

*******
v2020.03.08 changes:

(1) Added CD_DVD_label_for_Graduate_School.docx file.
(2) Renamed Forms folder to Forms_for_Undegraduate_School.
(3) Added undergraduate thesis evaluation files (PDF files in the Forms_for_Undegraduate_School folder).

By: LM
*******

*******
v2019.09.29 changes:

(1) Changed Associate to Assistant.
(2) Arranged TOC of Word version.

By: LM
*******

*******
v2019.09.26 changes:

(1) Fixed unnecessary white space in one of the sample tables.
(2) Added tables for deliverables, methods, and results per objective.
(3) Added a Word version.

By: LM
*******

*******
v2017.04.08 changes:

(1) Included the cropped PDF signed approval sheet
(2) Put accomplished student research ethics clearance in the appendix

By: LM
*******

*******
v2017.03.12 changes:

(1) Changed \approvalDate to \finalDefenseDate, and clarified its use
(2) Added RASD in approval sheet for graduate theses
(3) Clarified descriptions in the results and discussions and conclusions chapters
(4) Added appendices on the revisions based on the panelist comments. 
(5) Added breaking of long cites.
(6) Added web link to the template

By: LM
*******

*******
v2016.10.14 changes:

(1) Added commands for text coloring/highlighting.
(2) Clarified Prior Studies and Literature Review Differences.
(3) Renamed Overview to Overview of (document type), clarified assumptions, scope, and delimitations.
(4) Use APA as default citation format instead of IEEE.
(5) Clarified descriptions of expected section and chapter contents.

By: LM
*******

*******
v2016.08.05 changes:

(1) In document.tex: changed style=dict for the glossary
(2) Added versioning number to a PDF file field
(3) Placed some descriptions of commonly expected contents in certain chapters and sections.
(4) Generalized terms based on the document type. 
(5) Added files for notations, LaTeX math, citation, style, and abbreviation of bibliography entries
(6) Separated files before TOC
(7) Changed versioning number to YYYY.MM.DD format
(8) Renamed some files 
(9) Corrected only those grammatical & spelling mistakes that have been detected
(10) Added (a) usage examples on citation, and (b) IEEE styles

By: LM
*******

*******
2016-Jun-26
V0.13 changes:

(1) In usage_example.tex: Fixed equations listing to reflect the actual code. 
(2) In usage_example.tex: Added page numbers in the section "Adding Relevant PDF Pages." 
(3) Renamed example.pdf in the figure directory to example_gray_box.pdf
(4) Fixed the double Approval Sheet for the graduate school format
(5) Added the preparation guide in the Abstract

By: LM
*******

*******
2015-May-26 
V0.12 changes:

(1) In usage_example.tex: Fixed hanging \boldmath and Index example. Improved notation, figure, table, referencing, algorithm/pseudocode/code listing examples. 

(2) Modified documentType to Thesis instead of Thesis Proposal

(3) Corrected last missing 0 in ISO 8000-2 (the correct one is ISO 80000-2)

(4) Corrected some grammatical errors (there might be more left).

By: LM
*******

*******
2015-May-25 
V0.1 changes:

(1) Tried to fix the "Improper Alphabetic Constant" error.

(2) Placed additional examples in usage_example.tex

By: LM
*******

*******
25-May-2015 original LaTeX2e version:

by LM
Department of Electronics and Communications Engineering
De La Salle University, Manila, Philippines
*******

*******
2015-March-17 
V0.0:

(1) Released to Engr. AD

By: LM
*******

